MACKENZIE CHOY

OBJECTIVE

Highly motivated Business Information Technology student seeking a job in web development. I have a strong passion for learning new skills and I excel in a team environment developed through five years of customer service experience.

Website: https://mackenziechoy.com

Github: https://github.com/mchoy30

EDUCATION

BUSINESS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY DIPLOMA- RED RIVER COLLEGE

January 2017- April 2019

This two-year program provides a solid foundation in information technology with a focus on the following technical areas: Application Development, Web Development, Database Management, and Network Management.

INTRODUCTION BUSINESS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY CERTIFICATE- RED RIVER COLLEGE September 2016 - December 2016

This certificate is a four-month preparatory program for the Business Information Technology program with a focus on the following areas: Introduction to Programming Logic, Business Computing, Business Math, and Financial Accounting.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Programming Languages: C#, Java, SQL
- Experience in web frameworks Vue.JS and React
- Experience with Google Firebase web services
- Web Development Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP
- Skillful in troubleshooting basic workstation problems
- Windows Server, Server Troubleshooting, Active Directory
- Expereniced in the Microsoft Office Suite (2010 and 2016)
- Qualified in Adobe products (Acrobat and Reader)
- Familiar with Remote desktop support

NON-TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- Great commination skills with customers
- Proficient in writing and composing email to clients
- Able to work well with a team
- A very dependable and initiative worker
- Composed under pressure

EXPERIENCE

Support Analysist, Health Canada

May 2018- December 2018

Used trouble shooting skills to solve various IT related problems

Assisted clients with various software and hardware issues both on site and remotely

Organized various IT equipment and followed the proper policies and procedures in order to surplus them.

Scheduled appointments with clients to help them with their IT issues.

MOTIVATOR, GOODLIFE FITNESS

February 2015- August 2017

Motivated and trained members of the GoodLife Fitness. Delivered high quality experiences and was considered the information source for all member and prospective members. Responsible for handing and cleaning members equipment. Created and processed paperwork dealing with confidential information.

DELI CLERK, SUPERSTORE

July 2013 - June 2015

Provided premier customer service, including greeting them and responding to questions. Maintained Superstores high standards for product freshness and sanitations. Responsible for providing for creating orders worth over \$1,000. Dynamically sold product by providing customers with information needed to make product related decisions.

VOLUNTEERED AS AN SPECIAL EVENT ASSISTANT, OAKVIEW PLACE

The summers of 2013, 2014, and 2015

Devised and created events to entertain guests and residents. Cared for residents and developed meaningful relationships. Helped with general inquiries about Oakview place. Participated in setting up and taking down events.

VOLUNTEERED IN FAMILY BUSINESS, HUSH & SHOUT CLOTHING

The summer of 2015

Organized and co-planned outdoor store layouts. Responsible for maintaining product stock and placing order when stock was low. Interacted with customers at the store and maintained the in-store transactions.

INTERESTS

Chess, Latin Dance, Cooking Bodybuilding, Guitar, Billiards, Tennis

REFERENCES

STEVE TYSON

Team Lead
Health Canada
391 York Avenue
Winnipeg, Manitoba R3C 0P4
204-594-8034
Steve.tyson@canada.ca

JESSICA BEAUGRAND

Assistant Manager GoodLife Fitness 319 Portage Ave Winnipeg, Manitoba R3K 0W4 (204) 390-0065

SCOTT WACHAL

Web Development/Programming Instructor Red River College 160 Princess Street Winnipeg, MB R3B 1K9 (204) 949-8318 swachal@rrc.ca

CRISTINE BOLDUC

Head of Renovations Superstore Canada (204) 228-0987